Oh, my God, do you smell gas?
(Raj:)- No.
- Yeah, no.
PENNY:
You know, they have DVDs over there.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but they have DVD burners
over here.
(Sheldon:)Leonard needs a DVD burner.
(Penny:)Sheldon, a gift shouldn't be
something someone needs.
(Penny:)It should be something fun.
- Something they wouldn't buy for themself.
- You mean, like a sweater?
(Penny:)Well, it's a fun sweater.
It's got a bold geometric print.
- Is it the geometry that makes it fun?
- Okay.
(Penny:)The point is, one of the ways
we show we care about people...
(Penny:)...is by putting thought and imagination
into the gifts we give them.
- Okay, I see, so not a DVD burner.
- Exactly.
(Sheldon:)Something he wouldn't buy for himself,
something fun, something like... Ah!
An 802. 11n wireless router.